{
    "subject": "resource/Louis,_Duke_of_Burgundy",
    "predicate": "ontology/restingPlace",
    "object": "resource/France",
    "human_readable": "Louis, Duke of Burgundy's resting place is France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9509003758430481,
            "question": "What was the resting place of Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9315130114555359,
            "question": "Where is Louis, Duke of Burgundy laid to rest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9292798042297363,
            "question": "Is Louis, Duke of Burgundy buried in France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151380062103271,
            "question": "Was France the burial location of Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8187674880027771,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Louis, Duke of Burgundy's final resting place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6741105318069458,
            "question": "Where is Louis, Duke of Burgundy buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5694633722305298,
            "question": "In which country did Louis, Duke of Burgundy die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5622804760932922,
            "question": "Is there any information about Louis, Duke of Burgundy's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5223029851913452,
            "question": "What is known about the end of Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46931397914886475,
            "question": "Where did Louis, Duke of Burgundy spend his final years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis, Duke of Burgundy's resting place is France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3618_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about the end of Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3618_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Louis, Duke of Burgundy's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3618_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Louis, Duke of Burgundy die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3618_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3618_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\n* **The documents state:** \"The funeral procession of Louis and his wife, Marie-Adelaide de Savoy, to be buried at the Basilica of Saint Denis in Paris.\"  \n* **Saint Denis is located in France.**\n\n\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Louis, Duke of Burgundy's resting place is France\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Louis de France, Duke of Burgundy was to be buried at the Basilica of Saint Denis in Paris, which is in France. Therefore, the statement that Louis, Duke of Burgundy's resting place is France is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}